hdtvku.com 2018-06-09

# HDTVKU

This Privacy Policy was last updated on December 31, 2017

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Hdtvku collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://hdtvku.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Hdtvku.

Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

How we use collected information

Hdtvku collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

If you submit personally identifiable information to us through Hdtvku, we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the general and personalized features and functionality of the Hdtvku Site, and to process any flagging activity or correspondence you send to us. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload videos, photos or send messages through the Hdtvku Site and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any videos or photos that you submit to the Hdtvku Site may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Hdtvku Site changes or for customer service purposes). We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Hdtvku Site and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, analyzing, and processing user preferences and trends, as well as user activity and communications. We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Hdtvku Site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.

Changes to this privacy policy

Hdtvku has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

For more information you may contact Hdtvku through email form available on hdtvku.com
